<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Spoken Tutorials</string>

    <string name="sample_content">An initiative of National Mission on Education through ICT, Government of India, to promote IT literacy through Open Source Software.
        
    </string><string name="sample_use">To know more about this free service using audio-video tutorials just drag the entire window.\nand click on menu items.</string>

    <string name="sample_window">Sample of dragging the entire window.\nThe menu is a simple ScrollView, with a click
        listener set on each item.\nThe drawer will animate slightly open, to make it more discoverable.\nAdditionally,
        if the menu is open, a back press will close it.
    </string>

    <string name="sample_listactivity">Sample of how to use the drawer with ListActivity.\nWhen running on ICS or
        greater, the ActionBar up button will blink until clicked by the user. This is done to make the menu more
        discoverable.\nAdditionally, if the menu is open, a back press will close it.
    </string>

    <string name="sample_rightmenu">This sample shows how to position the menu to the right of the content.\nRun on
        an API14+ device to see how it interacts with the overflow button.
    </string>

    <string name="sample_topmenu">This sample shows how to position the menu above the content.</string>

    <string name="sample_bottommenu">This sample shows how to position the menu below the content.</string>

    <string name="sample_layout">This sample shows how to use the drawer in a layout file.
        \nThe top drawer is used in this sample.
    </string>

    <string name="sample_static">This sample shows how to attach a drawer that is always visible.</string>
    
    <string name="msg_content">
        Hello,\n
        I would like you to conduct workshop in our college.\n
        Please reply me with necessary details.\n
        Thank you.\n
        </string>
        
    <string-array name="software_subtitle">
        <item>Advanced c c++</item>
        <item >Command language interpreter</item>
        <item>Blender is a free open source 3D graphics application, available under the GNU General Public License for the Linux, Mac OS X, FreeBSD, OpenBSD and Microsoft Windows operating systems. </item>
        <item>Powerful features, simple syntax, and portability make C a preferred language among programmers for business and industrial applications</item>
 	    <item>CellDesigner is a SBML compliant software , it is process diagram editor for drawing gene-regulatory and biochemical networks</item>
        <item>A digital divide is an economic inequality between groups, broadly construed, in terms of access to, use of, or knowledge of information and communication technologies (ICT)</item>
        <item>Drupal is a free and open source content management system (CMS) written in PHP and distributed under the GNU General Public License</item>
        <item>Mozilla Firefox or simply Firefox is a free, open source web browser,it is the default web browser for Ubuntu Linux. </item>
        <item>GChemPaint is a 2D chemical structures editor for the Gnome-2 desktop.</item>
        <item>GeoGebra is an interactive geometry software for education in schools. GeoGebra is written in Java and thus available for multiple platforms</item>
        <item>GeoGebra is an interactive geometry, algebra, and calculus application, intended for teachers and students</item>
        <item>GIMP (GNU Image Manipulation Program) is a free software raster graphics editor</item>
        <item>It allow to simulate complex network. It works on windows, Linux and Mac OS based machines</item>
        <item>Web based accounting software</item>
        <item >Schemantic capture. Gschem is part of the project gEDA</item>
        <item>It is a free and open source high level programming language,simple as well as object oriented language</item>
        <item >Java EE technology</item>
        <item>KiCad is a open source(GPL) integrated package for electronics design automation(EDA),used for designing schematics of electronics circuits and printed circuit board(PCB)</item>
        <item>KTouch is a typing tutor,it teaches you how to type using an online interactive keyboard</item>
        <item>KTurtle is an educational programming environment that aims to make learning how to program as easy as possible</item>
        <item>LaTeX is a high-quality typesetting system,it includes features designed for the production of technical and scientific documentation</item>
        <item>LibreOffice Base is the database front-end of the LibreOffice suite,Base is the equivalent of Microsoft Access</item>
        <item>It is the equivalent of Microsoft Excel in Microsoft Suite and has a number of unique features, including a system which automatically defines series of graphs, based on information available to the user</item>
        <item>LibreOffice is a graphics software that allows you to create a wide range of vector graphics</item>
        <item>Spreadsheet component of LibreOffice software </item>
        <item>LibreOffice Math is a software application designed for creating and editing mathematical formulae</item>
        <item>LibreOffice Writer is the word processor component of the LibreOffice Suite.It is the equivalent of Microsoft Word in Microsoft Office Suite</item>
        <item>Linux is one of the most popular Operating Systems used in todays world</item>
        <item>NetBeans IDE supports development of all Java application types (Java SE including JavaFX, (Java ME, web, EJB and mobile applications)NetBeans refers to both a platform framework for Java desktop applications</item>
        <item>Ngspice is a general-purpose Electrical / Electronics circuit simulation program for nonlinear and linear analysis</item>
        <item>OpenFOAM (Open Source Field Operation and Manipulation) is a free, open source CFD software package developed by the OpenFOAM Team at SGI(Silicon Graphics International) Corporation and distributed by the OpenFOAM Foundation</item>
        <item>Orca is a Free and Open source screen reader that works in GNU/Linux operating system</item>
        <item>Perl (Practical Extraction and Reporting Language) is widely used open-source language</item>
        <item>PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor" is a widely-used Open Source general-purpose scripting language that is especially suited for Web development and can be embedded into HTML</item>
        <item>Numerical computational software for Science and Engineering Education - used in 3D animation and Gaming industry, Artificial Intelligence, YouTube, NASA, CERN, Yahoo and so on</item>
        <item>Numerical computational software for Science and Engineering Education - used in 3D animation and Gaming industry, Artificial Intelligence, YouTube, NASA, CERN, Yahoo and so on</item>
        <item>QCAD is an application for computer aided drafting in two dimensions (2d)</item>
        <item>Ruby an absolutely pure object-oriented scripting language and a genuine attempt to combine the best of everything in the scripting world</item>
        <item>Mathematical and scientific calculation software, open source substitute for MATLAB, very useful for all science and engineering students, in academics particularly. </item>
        <item>Selenium is an open source Test Automation tool which has rich set of testing functions and the operations are highly flexible</item>
        <item>A single-board heater system is a low cost, open source, lab-in-a-box setup</item>
        <item>STEP is an interactive tool for learning Physics. Using this tool, you can model the physical world through simulations</item>
        <item>The Spoken Tutorials for Thunderbird are being contributed by DesiCrew Solutions, Chennai</item>
        <item>Tux Typing provides the following important features:Start typing,Practice lessons,Play a game,Set language for typing</item>
        <item>Free,open source,cross-platform email,news and chat client developed by Mozilla Foundation</item>
        <item>Xfig is an interactive drawing tool which runs under X Window System on most UNIX-compatible platforms</item>
        
    </string-array>
    <string name="query1">SELECT wr.cfm_wkshop_date, wr.foss_category, ac.id, ac.institution_name, ac.state_code, ac.city FROM workshop_requests wr, academic_center ac WHERE wr.cfm_wkshop_date > \'\".DATE("Y-m-d").\"\' and wr.status=1 and ac.academic_code=wr.academic_code ORDER BY wr.cfm_wkshop_date, wr.cfm_wkshop_time ASC</string>
    <string name="query2">SELECT st.name, st.code, rp.rp_fname, rp.phone, u.mail FROM states st, resource_person rp, CDEEP.users u where FIND_IN_SET(st.code, rp.states) > 0 and rp.user_uid=u.uid and rp.state_code!=\"\"</string>
    <string name="query3">SELECT distinct td.foss_category from CDEEP.tutorial_resources tr, CDEEP.tutorial_details td where tr.tutorial_status=\'accepted\' and tr.tutorial_detail_id=td.id  ORDER BY td.foss_category ASC</string>
    
    </resources>
